skyliteshop.com 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

:To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

: To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

: To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

: To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

: To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

: To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes we use cookies to improve the browsing experience for our users.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.skyliteshop.com/terms%20-%20and%20-%20conditions

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

This policy was last modified on 30.10.2013

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.skylitegroup.com  
Variskuja 1  
Vantaa, Uusimaa 01450  
Finland  
info@skylitegroup.com

_This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance scans._
